A Guide to the Asia Society records FA110
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Public Affairs, Southeast Asia Development Advisory Group (SEADAG), 1961-1980; 1
  - SEADAG Audio Tapes, 11
    - SEADAG (Southeast Asia Development Advisory Group) (1), 1967 February 18 (Box 120)
    - SEADAG (Southeast Asia Development Advisory Group) (2), 1967 February 18 (Box 120)
    - SEADAG (Southeast Asia Development Advisory Group) (3), 1967 February 18 (Box 120)
    - SEADAG (Southeast Asia Development Advisory Group), 1966 October 21-22 (Box 120)
    - SEADAG (Southeast Asia Development Advisory Group) Thursday 4:00-5:30 (Box 120)
    - SEADAG (Southeast Asia Development Advisory Group) J.Krutilla Asia House, 3 3/4, 1968 November 1 (Box 120)
    - SEADAG (Southeast Asia Development Advisory Group) Friday No. 4 (Box 120)
    - SEADAG (Southeast Asia Development Advisory Group) Asia House, 3 3/4, 1966 September 30 (Box 120)
    - SEADAG (Southeast Asia Development Advisory Group) Jan Mekong Seminrar, 1st Session, 1967 January 25 (Box 120)
    - SEADAG (Southeast Asia Development Advisory Group) Jan Mekong Seminar, 2nd Session, 1967 January 25 (Box 120)
    - SEADAG (Southeast Asia Development Advisory Group), 1:30-3, 3 3/4, Asia House Library, No. 1, Jan Mekong Seminar, 1967 January 24 (Box 120)
    - SEADAG (Southeast Asia Development Advisory Group), 3-5, 3 3/4, Asia House Library, No. 2, Jan Mekong Sem, 1967 January 24 (Box 120)
    - SEADAG (Southeast Asia Development Advisory Group), Gustav Papanek's seminar: "Indonesia", 1976 May 14-16 (Box 120)
    - Tapes T1-T22, with inauguration speech tape and last conclusion speech tape, 1976 September 5-9 (Box 120)
    - Tape - Urban seminar 1, 1967 February 11 (Box 121)
    - Tape - Urban Seminar 2, 1967 February 11 (Box 121)
    - Tape - Urban Seminar 3, 1967 February 11 (Box 121)
    - SEADAG-Plenary-Asia Society, Tape 1, 1967 April 15 (Box 121)
    - SEADAG-Plenary-Asia Society, Tape 2, 1967 April 15 (Box 121)
    - SEADAG-Plenary, Asia House, Tape 1, 1967 April 14 (Box 121)
    - SEADAG-Plenary, Asia House, Tape 2, 1967 April 14 (Box 121)
    - SEADAG-Plenary, Asia House, Tape 3, 1967 April 14 (Box 121)
    - SEADAG-Plenary-Asia Society, Tape 3, 1967 April 15 (Box 121)
    - SEADAG - Executive Committee, Tape 1, 1966 February 1 (Box 121)
    - SEADAG - Executive Committee, Tape 2, 1966 February 1 (Box 121)
    - SEADAG - Executive Committee, Tape 3, February 23 (Box 121)
    - SEADAG - Executive Committee, Tape 4, February 23 (Box 121)
    - SEADAG - Mid Morning, Tape 1, 1967 January 18 (Box 121)
    - SEADAG, 12:00pm Tape, 1967 January 18 (Box 121)
    - SEADAG - Executive committee, February 23 Tape (Box 121)
    - SEADAG - Asia House 2nd Tape, 1966 December 3 (Box 121)
    - SEADAG - Executive committee, February 23 tape (Box 121)
    - SEADAG - Tape - Thursday 9:30-11 Green Revolution (Box 121)
    - SEADAG - Tape - June 25 - Morning Start (Box 121)
    - SEADAG - Tape - June 25 - Afternoon continued (Box 121)
    - SEADAG Tape - 9:30-11:15 Green Revolution (Box 121)
    - SEADAG Tape - Friday No. 2 - Green Revolution (Box 121)
    - SEADAG Tape- 12:30 Luncheon Discussion Side No. 1, October 21. 9:45 Young, Tieman, Nimblock, Discussion October 24, Side No. 2. (Box 121)
    - SEADAG Tape - No. 1 2:35 to 3:40, Asia House Library, 1966 November 15 (Box 121)
    - SEADAG Tape - No. 2 3:50-5:25, Asia House Library, 1966 November 15 (Box 121)
    - SEADAG Tape - Rural Development Seminar, December 18-19 (Box 121)
    - Tape 122, 1972 March 22 (Box 121)
    - Tape 324 (Box 121)
    - Tape 526 (Box 121)
    - SEADAG audio tapes (42 tapes), 1967-1969 (Box 122)
- Country Councils, 1951-1988; 2
  Series 2: Country Councils
  Subseries 1: Country Councils – General
  Subseries 2: China Council Files
  Subseries 3: India Council Files
  Subseries 4: Mary Ann Siegfried (MAS) Files
  See also: Series 1 and Series 8.
  - Country Councils - General, 1
    - Country Councils - General (Box 123, Folder 1263)
    - Country Councils - Bangladesh, 1971-1972 (Box 123, Folder 1264)
    - Country Councils - Pakistan - Boston Committee, 1972 (Box 123, Folder 1265)
    - Country Councils - Pakistan - Washington Committee, 1972 (Box 123, Folder 1266)
    - Country Councils - Pakistan - Speakers (Box 123, Folder 1267)
    - Country Councils - Pakistan - Speakers Correspondence, 1972 (Box 123, Folder 1268)
    - Country Councils - Pakistan - India-Pakistan Relations, 1971 (Box 123, Folder 1269)
    - Country Councils - Pakistan - General, 1972 (Box 123, Folder 1270)
    - Country Councils - Pakistan - Pakistan Cyclone Relief - Benefit showing of "Of Men and Rivers" (Box 123, Folder 1271)
    - Country Councils - Pakistan - Pakistan Cyclone Relief - Notes and Clippings, 1970 (Box 123, Folder 1272)
    - Country Councils - Pakistan - Pakistan Cyclone Relief (Box 123, Folder 1273)
    - Country Councils - Pakistan - Membership lists, 1970 (Box 123, Folder 1274)
    - Country Councils - Pakistan - Phillips Talbot Diary - Trip to Pakistan, 1971 (Box 123, Folder 1275)
    - Country Councils - Pakistan - Akhter Hameed Khan - Reception and Roundtable, 1969 September 17 (Box 123, Folder 1276)
    - Country Councils - Pakistan - Annual Dinner, 1968 December 3 (Box 123, Folder 1277)
    - Country Councils - Pakistan - Zulfikar Al Butto- Clippings, 1968-1970 (Box 123, Folder 1278)
    - Country Councils - Pakistan - Zulfikar Al Butto trip (cancelled), 1967-1969 (Box 124, Folder 1279)
    - Country Councils - Pakistan - Zulfikar Al Butto trip (cancelled), 1967-1969 (Box 124, Folder 1280)
    - Country Councils - Malaysia / Singapore - Contemporary Artists of Malaysia: A Bibliographic Survey - by Dolores Wharton, 1971 (Box 124, Folder 1281)
    - Country Councils - Malaysia / Singapore, 1967-1971 (Box 124, Folder 1282)
    - Country Councils - Malaysia, 1962-1969 (Box 124, Folder 1283)
    - Country Councils - Malaysia - Supplemental material, 1960-1965 (Box 124, Folder 1284)
    - Country Councils - Malaysia - Formation of Council and Lists (membership and invitation), 1965-1966 (Box 124, Folder 1285)
    - Country Councils - Malaysia - Chuah Thean Teng (Batik paintings / exhibit), 1967-1968 (Box 124, Folder 1286)
    - Country Councils - Malaysia - Gayl Ness - Chair, 1966-1968 (Box 124, Folder 1287)
    - Country Councils - Malaysia - Membership lists and correspondence, 1965-1969 (Box 124, Folder 1288)
    - Country Councils - Malaysia - Programs, 1968-1969 (Box 125, Folder 1289)
    - Country Councils - Malaysia - Programs, 1967-1968 (Box 125, Folder 1290)
    - Country Councils - Malaysia - Programs, 1966-1967 (Box 125, Folder 1291)
    - Country Councils - Malaysia - Programs, 1965-1966 (Box 125, Folder 1292)
    - Country Councils - Malaysia - Visitors, 1967-1968 (Box 125, Folder 1293)
    - Country Councils - Singapore - 1967-1969 (Box 125, Folder 1294)
    - Country Councils - Singapore - Lee Kuan Yew reception, 1967 October 20 (Box 125, Folder 1295)
    - Country Councils - Singapore - Lee Yuan Yew visit, 1967 October 20, 22; 1967-1968 (Box 125, Folder 1296)
    - Country Councils - Pakistan - Correspondence, 1962-1970 (Box 125, Folder 1297)
    - Country Councils - Pakistan - Supplemental material, 1963-1970 (Box 125, Folder 1298)
    - Country Councils - Pakistan - Pakistan Students Association of America, 1966-1969 (Box 125, Folder 1299)
    - Country Councils - Pakistan - Mirzah Ghalib lecture, 1970 April 28 (Box 125, Folder 1300)
    - Country Councils - Pakistan - Pakistan Cyclone Relief Committee, 1970-1971 (Box 125, Folder 1301)
    - Country Councils - Pakistan - Print Council of America - American Prints Today, 1962-1966 (Box 125, Folder 1302)
    - Asia Society Country Councils - Pakistan - J. Iqbal Geoffrey, 1962-1967 (Box 126, Folder 1303)
    - Country Councils - A.J. Shemza, 1960-1963 (Box 126, Folder 1304)
    - Country Councils - Pakistan - Brochure (Description of Pakistan Council), 1967 (Box 126, Folder 1305)
    - Country Councils - Pakistan - Membership Lists, 1970 (Box 126, Folder 1306)
    - Country Councils - Pakistan - Council Lists, 1962-1964 (Box 126, Folder 1307)
    - Country Councils - Pakistan - Programs, 1968-1969 (Box 126, Folder 1308)
    - Country Councils - Pakistan - Programs, 1961-1964 (Box 126, Folder 1309)
    - Country Councils - Pakistan, 1971-1972 (Box 126, Folder 1310)
    - Films, 1967-1971 (Box 126, Folder 1311)
    - Country Councils - Ceylon - Cookbook, 1969 (Box 126, Folder 1312)
    - Country Councils - Ceylon, 1963-1970 (Box 126, Folder 1313)
    - Country Councils - Ceylon - Membership lists, 1967 (Box 126, Folder 1314)
    - Country Councils - Ceylon - International Conference on Ceylon, 1967 August 9-11 (Box 126, Folder 1315)
    - Country Councils - Ceylon - Programs - Vesak Festival, 1964 (Box 126, Folder 1316)
    - Country Councils - Ceylon - Programs, 1963-1969 (Box 127, Folder 1317)
    - Country Councils - Ceylon - Programs, 1963-1971 (Box 127, Folder 1318)
    - Country Councils - Ceylon - Programs - Religious Conference (Box 127, Folder 1319)
    - Country Councils - Ceylon - "Dilemmas of a new nation - " Wriggins - Howard, 1965 December 14 (Box 127, Folder 1320)
    - Country Councils - Ceylon - "Ceylon: Twenty years of Independence" Wriggins - Howard - et al., 1968 March 7 (Box 127, Folder 1321)
    - Country Councils - Ceylon - Information Department Reports, 1963 (Box 127, Folder 1322)
    - Country Councils - Ceylon - Senaka Senanayke Show, 1965-1968 (Box 127, Folder 1323)
    - Country Councils - Cambodia - Classical Khmer Ballet, 1971 (Box 127, Folder 1324)
    - Angkor Watt photography show, 1971 (Box 127, Folder 1325)
    - Country Councils - Cambodia, 1963-1970 (Box 127, Folder 1326)
    - Country Councils - Cambodia - Supplemental material, undated (Box 127, Folder 1327)
    - Country Councils - Cambodia - Correspondent's Roundatable, 1971 April 4 (Box 127, Folder 1328)
    - Country Councils - Thailand, 1966-1970 (Box 128, Folder 1329)
    - Country Councils - Thailand, 1966-1970 (Box 128, Folder 1330)
    - Country Councils - Thailand, 1966-1970 (Box 128, Folder 1331)
    - Country Councils - Thailand, 1966-1970 (Box 128, Folder 1332)
    - Country Councils - Thailand - Association for Asian Studies, 1966 (Box 128, Folder 1333)
    - Country Councils - Thailand - Supplemental material, 1962-1967 (Box 128, Folder 1334)
    - Country Councils - Thailand - U.S. Thai Relations Seminar Series, 1967-1968 (Box 128, Folder 1335)
    - Country Councils - Thailand - Reception, 1971 (Box 128, Folder 1336)
    - Country Councils - Thailand - Siam Society, 1970-1971 (Box 128, Folder 1337)
    - Country Councils - Thailand - Programs - Hilltribes, 1966 (Box 128, Folder 1338)
    - Country Councils - Thailand - Programs, 1963-1971 (Box 129, Folder 1339)
    - East Asian Parliamentary Group, 1971 (Box 129, Folder 1340)
    - Country Councils - China- Programs - "Science and Medicine in the People's Republic of China", 1972 (Box 129, Folder 1341)
    - Country Councils - China- Programs - Speech by Rep. Patsy T. Mink, 1971 October 27 (Box 129, Folder 1342)
    - Country Councils - Programs - Lecture Series, 1980s, 1974 (Box 129, Folder 1343)
    - Country Councils - Afghanistan, 1970-1973 (Box 129, Folder 1344)
    - Country Councils - Bangladesh, 1972-1974 (Box 129, Folder 1345)
    - Country Councils - Burma, 1970-1974 (Box 129, Folder 1346)
    - Country Councils - Burma, 1970-1975 (Box 129, Folder 1347)
    - Country Councils - Burma, 1970-1975 (Box 129, Folder 1348)
    - Country Councils - Burma - Ramayana Workshop, 1975 March 7 (Box 129, Folder 1349)
    - Country Councils - Ceylon, 1971-1973 (Box 129, Folder 1350)
    - Country Councils - China, 1972 (Box 129, Folder 1351)
    - Country Councils - Himalayas, 1970-1973 (Box 129, Folder 1352)
    - Country Councils - Himalayas, 1970-1973 (Box 130, Folder 1353)
    - Country Councils - Himalayas, 1970-1973 (Box 130, Folder 1354)
    - Country Councils - Himalayas, 1970-1973 (Box 130, Folder 1355)
    - Country Councils - Indonesia, 1970-1973 (Box 130, Folder 1356)
    - Country Councils - Korea, 1972-1973 (Box 130, Folder 1357)
    - Country Councils - Malaysia/Singapore, 1970-1974 (Box 130, Folder 1358)
    - Country Councils - Pakistan, 1971-1974 (Box 130, Folder 1359)
    - Country Councils - Pakistan, 1971-1974 (Box 130, Folder 1360)
    - Country Councils - Pakistan, 1971-1974 (Box 130, Folder 1361)
    - Country Councils - Pakistan, 1971-1974 (Box 130, Folder 1362)
    - Country Councils - Philippines, 1971-1972 (Box 131, Folder 1363)
    - Country Councils - Thailand, 1970-1974 (Box 131, Folder 1364-1365)
    - Country Councils - Vietnam, 1973 (Box 131, Folder 1366)
    - Country Councils - Programs by Council, 1970-1974 (Box 131, Folder 1367)
    - Country Councils - Programs by Council, 1970-1974 (Box 131, Folder 1368)
    - Programs - Interest In, 1973 (Box 131, Folder 1369)
    - Country Councils - Membership lists (Chairmen), 1970-1971 (Box 131, Folder 1370)
    - Country Councils - Membership lists (by County), 1969-1971 (Box 131, Folder 1371)
    - Country Council - Events, 1962-1970 (Box 131, Folder 1372-1373)
    - Asia Council - Events - "Modernization in Asia: Problems and Opportunities", 1969 (Box 131, Folder 1374)
    - Country Councils - Asia Council, 1968-1969 (Box 132, Folder 1375)
    - Country Councils - Chairmen meetings, 1966-1968 (Box 132, Folder 1376)
    - Country Councils - Budgets, 1964-1970 (Box 132, Folder 1377)
    - Country Councils - (formation - Policy?), 1962-1970 (Box 132, Folder 1378)
    - Country Councils - Chairmen, 1967 (Box 132, Folder 1379)
    - Country Councils - Public Education, 1966 (Box 132, Folder 1380)
    - Burma, 1968 (Box 132, Folder 1381)
    - Chairmen's Minutes, 1966 (Box 132, Folder 1382)
    - Country Councils - JDR 3rd Fund Fellows, 1970 (Box 132, Folder 1383)
    - Country Councils - Budget, 1970-1971 (Box 132, Folder 1384)
    - Country Councils - Afghanistan - Peace Corps Volunteer, 1971 (Box 132, Folder 1385)
    - Country Councils - Thailand, 1971 (Box 132, Folder 1386)
    - Country Councils - Indonesia, 1969 (Box 132, Folder 1387)
    - Country Councils - Indonesia - Events, 1962-1963 (Box 132, Folder 1388)
    - Country Councils - Indonesia, 1968-1970 (Box 132, Folder 1389)
    - Country Councils - Indonesia, 1968-1970 (Box 133, Folder 1390)
    - Country Councils - Indonesia, 1968-1970 (Box 133, Folder 1391)
    - Country Councils - Indonesia, 1968-1970 (Box 133, Folder 1392-1393)
    - Country Councils - Ceylon - Information sheets, 1963-1964 (Box 133, Folder 1394)
    - Country Councils - Ceylon, 1959-1965 (Box 133, Folder 1395)
    - Country Councils - Ceylon, 1959-1965 (Box 133, Folder 1396)
    - Country Councils - Thailand - supplemental material, 1963-1965 (Box 133, Folder 1397)
    - Country Councils - Thailand, 1964-1965 (Box 133, Folder 1398)
    - Country Councils - Korea - "The Faces of Asia: Bridge of No Return" - NET Broadcast, 1968 April 29 (Box 134, Folder 1399)
    - Country Councils - Korea, 1964-1971 (Box 134, Folder 1400)
    - Country Councils - Korea, 1964-1971 (Box 134, Folder 1401)
    - Country Councils - Korea, 1964-1971 (Box 134, Folder 1402)
    - Country Councils - Korea - Events, 1969-1970 (Box 134, Folder 1403)
    - Country Councils - Vietnam - Supplemental material, 1956-1966 (Box 134, Folder 1404)
    - Country Councils - India - Indian Music, 1965-1970 (Box 134, Folder 1405)
    - Country Councils - India - Asian Music and Dance, 1967-1968 (Box 134, Folder 1406)
    - Country Councils - Nepal - Nepal Newsletter, 1967-1970 (Box 135, Folder 1407)
    - Country Councils - Himalayas, 1971 (Box 135, Folder 1408)
    - Country Councils - Nepal, 1961-1970 (Box 135, Folder 1409)
    - Mongolia Society - John G. Hangin, 1961-1970 (Box 135, Folder 1410)
    - Country Councils - Nepal - Events, 1961-1967 (Box 135, Folder 1411)
    - Country Councils - Nepal - Stella Kamrisch, 1966 (Box 135, Folder 1412)
    - Country Councils - Nepal, 1960 (Box 135, Folder 1413)
    - Country Councils - Nepal - Events, 1960 (Box 135, Folder 1414)
    - Country Councils - Nepal - Sikkam, 1966-1967 (Box 135, Folder 1415)
    - Country Councils - Vietnam - Supplemental Material, 1960-1964 (Box 135, Folder 1416)
    - Country Councils - Tibet, 1961-1970 (Box 135, Folder 1417)
    - Country Councils - Tibet, 1961-1970 (Box 135, Folder 1418)
    - Country Councils - Laos, 1963, 1967 (Box 136, Folder 1419)
    - Country Councils - Vietnam, 1965, 1968 (Box 136, Folder 1420)
    - Country Councils - Iran, 1970 (Box 136, Folder 1421)
    - Japan, 1957-1967 (Box 136, Folder 1422)
    - Country Councils - Bangladesh, 1974-1975 (Box 136, Folder 1423)
    - Country Councils - Philippines, 1961-1970 (Box 136, Folder 1424)
    - Country Councils - Philippines, 1961-1970 (Box 136, Folder 1425)
    - Country Councils - Philippines America Society, 1968-1970 (Box 136, Folder 1426)
    - Philippines America Society - New York Assembly, 1968 (Box 136, Folder 1427)
    - Country Councils - Vietnam, 1971 (Box 136, Folder 1428)
    - American Friends of Vietnam, 1961-1967 (Box 136, Folder 1429)
    - Country Councils - Burma, 1969-1971 (Box 137, Folder 1430)
    - Country Councils - Burma - Denison University, 1966-1969 (Box 137, Folder 1431)
    - Country Councils - India, 1962-1965 (Box 137, Folder 1432)
    - Country Councils - India - Exhibition - 'Nehru: His Life and His India - ' 1965-1968 (Box 137, Folder 1433)
    - Country Councils - India - Minutes, 1963-1965 (Box 137, Folder 1434)
    - Country Councils - India - Paul Sherbert file, 1966-1967 (Box 137, Folder 1435)
    - Country Councils - India - Contemporary Indian Art, 1966 (Box 137, Folder 1436)
    - Country Councils - India - India Week, Boston, 1962-1963 (Box 137, Folder 1437)
    - Country Councils - India, 1966 July-August (Box 138, Folder 1438)
    - Country Councils - India - Correspondence, 1966 May-June (Box 138, Folder 1439)
    - Country Councils - India, 1967 (Box 138, Folder 1440)
    - Country Councils - India - Correspondence, 1966 February (Box 138, Folder 1441)
    - Country Councils - India - Correspondence, 1966 November-December (Box 138, Folder 1442)
    - Country Councils - India - Correspondence, 1966 October (Box 138, Folder 1443)
    - Country Councils - India - Correspondence, 1966 March-April (Box 138, Folder 1444)
    - Country Councils - India - Correspondence, 1966 January (Box 138, Folder 1445)
    - Country Councils - India - Correspondence, 1966 September (Box 138, Folder 1446)
    - Country Councils - Chairmen's Meetings, 1976 (Box 139, Folder 1447)
    - Country Councils - Thailand - Chulalong Korn Series, 1973-1975 (Box 139, Folder 1448)
    - Country Councils - Cambodia / Laos, 1975-1976 (Box 139, Folder 1449)
    - Country Councils - Burma - Programs, 1975-1976 (Box 139, Folder 1450)
    - Country Councils - Bangladesh, 1975-1976 (Box 139, Folder 1451)
    - Country Councils - Sri Lanka, 1975-1976 (Box 139, Folder 1452)
    - Country Councils - Malaysia / Singapore, 1975-1976 (Box 139, Folder 1453)
    - Country Councils - Burma, 1975-1976 (Box 139, Folder 1454)
    - Country Councils - Pakistans - Minutes, 1959-1972 (Box 139, Folder 1455)
    - Programs and Calendars, 1971-1972 (Box 139, Folder 1456)
    - Programs and Calendars, 1971-1972 (Box 139, Folder 1457)
    - Country Councils - Ceylon, 1962-1973 (Box 139, Folder 1458)
    - Country Councils - Burma, 1963-1970 (Box 140, Folder 1459)
    - Country Councils - India, 1959-1970 (Box 140, Folder 1460)
    - Seminars - The Asian City - Administrative file, 1974 (Box 140, Folder 1461)
    - Country Councils - Himalayas, 1960-1974 (Box 140, Folder 1462)
    - Country Councils - Malaysia / Singapore, 1965-1971 (Box 140, Folder 1463)
    - India - Urban Development (3 papers), 1972-1973 (Box 140, Folder 1464)
    - Seminars - Doing Business in Asia, 1973 (Box 140, Folder 1465)
    - Seminars - The Asian City - "Calcutta: Where do we go from here?" Asok Mitra, 1974 November 21 (Box 140, Folder 1466)
    - Seminars - The Asian City - "Metropolitan Manila: Development Problems and Prospects" - Douglas H. Keare, 1975 May 8 (Box 140, Folder 1467)
    - Seminars - The Asian City - "Kabul City" Nancy Hatch Dupree, 1975 February 7 (Box 140, Folder 1468)
    - Seminars - The Asian City - "Bankok: The Nature of Migration and Population Change in a Primate City" Sidney Goldstein, 1975 February 20 (Box 140, Folder 1469)
    - Seminars - The Asian City - "Urbanization - Law Lawyers - " Bhupen Mukerjee, 1975 February 14 (Box 140, Folder 1470)
    - Seminars - The Asian City - "Urbanization: the Maoist Model" Rhoads Murphey, 1974 November 7 (Box 140, Folder 1471)
    - Seminars - The Asian City - "Islamabad - A New City for Asia - "Shahid Javed Burki, 1975 March 6 (Box 141, Folder 1472)
    - Country Councils - Ceylon, 1972 (Box 141, Folder 1473)
    - Seminars - The Asian City - "Kathmandu: A Pre-Industrial City - " Sigurd Grava, 1974 December 12 (Box 141, Folder 1474)
    - Seminars - The Asian City - "Urban and Regional Planning for the Delhi-New Delhi Area" - Gerald Breese, 1975 March 20 (Box 141, Folder 1475)
    - Seminars - The Asian City - "Asia's Cities: Problems and Options - 'Kingsley Davis, 1974 October 24 (Box 141, Folder 1476)
    - The Asian City - "An Asian Dilemma: Environmental Issue of Urban Growth" - Khalid Shibli, 1975 April 18 (Box 141, Folder 1477)
    - United Nations - Committee for the Co-ordination of Investigations of the Lower MeKong Basin - Annual Report, 1972 (Box 141, Folder 1478)
    - United Nations - Committee for the Co-ordination of Investigations of the Lower MeKong Basin - Sub-committee Reports, 1970-1974 (Box 141, Folder 1479)
    - Phuket Project, 1978-1979 (Box 141, Folder 1480)
    - Administration - Corporate Members list, 1979 (Box 141, Folder 1481)
    - Events (Country Councils), 1977 (Box 141, Folder 1482)
    - Events (Country Councils), 1978 (Box 141, Folder 1483)
    - Events (Country Councils), 1976 (Box 141, Folder 1484)
    - Country Councils - Burma - Burmese Music and Dance Project (Box 141, Folder 1485)
    - Country Councils - Himalayas, 1975-1976 (Box 142, Folder 1486)
    - Country Councils - Thailand - Minutes, 1959-1962 (Box 142, Folder 1487)
    - Country Councils - Philippines - Minutes, 1959-1962 (Box 142, Folder 1488)
    - Country Councils - Pakistan - Minutes, 1958-1962 (Box 142, Folder 1489)
    - Country Councils - Indonesia - Minutes, 1962 (Box 142, Folder 1490)
    - Country Councils - Formation, 1962 (Box 142, Folder 1491)
    - Country Councils - Afghanistan - Minutes, 1963-1964 (Box 142, Folder 1492)
    - Country Councils - Indian Theater, 1957-1958 (Box 142, Folder 1493)
    - Country Councils - India - Indian Art and Artists, 1961 (Box 142, Folder 1494)
    - Administration, 1964 (Box 142, Folder 1495)
    - Country Councils - Burma - Supplemental Material, 1960-1963 (Box 142, Folder 1496)
    - Country Councils - Afghanistan, 1960-1962 (Box 142, Folder 1497)
    - Royal Cambodian Ballet (film), 1977-1978 (Box 142, Folder 1498)
    - Association of Southeast Asian Nations (ASEAN), 1977 (Box 142, Folder 1499)
    - Business Advisory Committee, 1977 (Box 142, Folder 1500)
    - Country Councils - India - Luncheon, 1977 May 19 (Box 142, Folder 1501)
    - Events - "The River" showing 1977 (Box 142, Folder 1502)
    - Events - U Thant Symposium, 1976-1977 (Box 142, Folder 1503)
    - Country Councils - Thailand - Seminar - "Southeast Asian Ceramics", 1976 (Box 142, Folder 1504)
    - Country Councils - Chairmen's Meetings, 1976-1977 (Box 142, Folder 1505)
    - ASEAN - Conference - "Financial Trends in the ASEAN Region" (not held), 1978-1979 (Box 143, Folder 1506)
    - ASEAN - Upadit Pachariyang Kun Luncheon, 1978 (Box 143, Folder 1507)
    - Events - Henry Luce Fellows Luncheon, 1978 (Box 143, Folder 1508)